my-true-self.com 2017-08-10

# my-true-self.com - Discover yourself!

### Scope

This data privacy statement is intended to inform the user as to the nature, extent and purpose of collecting and using personal data through this website by the vendor responsible for the site (fabulabs GmbH, Pappelallee 78/79, 10437 Berlin Germany).

### Access Data / Server Log Files

The vendor (or webspace provider) collects data on access to the site (so-called server log files). Access data includes: 

Name of the website accessed; files accessed and the date and time they were accessed; volume of data transmitted; notification of successful retrieval; browser type and version; user's operating system; referring URL (page previously visited), IP address and the requesting provider. 

The vendor uses the log files solely for statistical analysis for the purpose of operating, securing and improvement of the site. However, the vendor reserves the right to subsequently review the log files when there is specific evidence giving rise to the reasonable suspicion of illegal use.

### Cookies

Cookies are small files that allow specific information to be stored relating to the user's specific access device (PC, smartphone or the like). They serve, on the one hand, to benefit the user by making the site more user friendly (e.g. by storing login data). On the other hand, they also collect statistical data on website use in order to analyze that use for the purpose of improving the site. The user can influence the way cookies are stored and used. Most browsers have an option that allows the user to restrict or block the use of cookies. However, it must be noted that doing so will restrict use and in particular user friendliness of the site. 

You can manage many online ad cookies from private companies via the US website, <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or the EU site, <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices/>.

### Use of Personal Data

Personal data is information that can be used to identify a particular individual person, in other words, information that can be traced back to a specific individual person. This includes name, email address or telephone number. But personal data can also include information about preferences, hobbies, memberships or websites visited. Personal data may be collected and used by the vendor only where allowed by law or where the user has provided consent to the collection of his/her data.

### Registration

Data provided during registration will be employed in association with use of the site, in relation to site technical information and for sending newsletters and web mailings, where consent to such has been provided. Users can obtain information by email about the site or about registration, such as changes to the site or technical issues. The data being collected is entered in the fields that are filled in during registration. These include, for example, first name, last name, sex, email address, IP address and the date and time of registration. If a user registers through the authentication feature on Facebook, the user's Facebook ID will be stored, as well as, where applicable, information about the user's sex, date of birth, likes and friends list. The scope of data collected may be obtained through the Facebook login dialogue. The specific data that Facebook makes available can be found at the following link: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other>. 

Facebook makes the determination based on the provisions of its own data privacy policy as to which data will always be publically available and which data you can make private via your privacy settings. For the details, go to: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info>. 

If a user no longer wishes to make use of the Facebook application, the user can terminate the user agreement. To do so, the user must go to the so-called "App Center" in his/her Facebook settings and terminate the link between the app and his/her Facebook profile. Directions on how to do this can be found here: <https://www.facebook.com/help/121070141307903>. Please note: Deleting the app does not delete the user's profile data from the vendor's server. To delete this data, the user must submit a separate withdrawal of consent to the use of his/her data to the email address shown in the section on "Withdrawals".

### Consent to Receive Ads

**The user agrees to receive from the vendor messages containing informational or promotional materials from various business sectors via electronic channels (e.g. email, notifications or mobile push-notifications). However, this applies only where the user has explicitly provided consent (e.g. by a consent box). The user can withdraw such consent at any time (contact email address: see "Withdrawals").**

### Withdrawals, Modifications, Notifications and Updates

The user has the right to receive upon request and at no cost information about personal data being kept on him/her. In addition, the user has the right to be informed of incorrect data or if his/her personal data has been blocked or deleted, where there is no legal obligation to retain such data. Requests should be sent by email to the following email address: info@mein-wahres-ich.de.

### Use of Google Analytics with anonymization

Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service from Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, hereinafter referred to as "Google". Google Analytics employs so-called "cookies", text files that are stored to your computer in order to facilitate an analysis of your use of the site. The information generated by these cookies, such as time, place and frequency of your visits to our site, including your IP address, is transmitted to Google's location in the US and stored there. In using Google Analytics our website employs the extension, "_gat._anonymizeIp". In doing so, Google abbreviates and thereby anonymizes your IP address before transferring it from member states of the European Union or signatory states to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Google uses this information to analyze your use of our site, to compile reports for us on internet activity and to provide other services relating to website and internet use. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law or where such third parties process this data on Google's behalf. Google states that it will in never associate your IP address with other data held by Google. You can prevent cookies from being installed by adjusting the settings on your browser software accordingly. You should be aware, however, that by doing so you may not be able to make full use of all the functions of our website. Furthermore, Google offers a deactivation add-on for most current browsers that provides you with more control over what data Google can collect on websites you access. The add-on tells the JavaScript (ga.js) used by Google Analytics not to transmit any information about website visits to Google Analytics. However, the browser deactivation add-on offered by Google Analytics does not prevent information from being transmitted to us or to other web analysis services we may engage. You can find additional information on how to install the browser add-on at the following link: [](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de)

### Use of Google+ recommendation components

Our website employs the "+1"-buttom from Google+ belonging to Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, hereinafter referred to as "Google". Each time our website receives an access request equipped with a "+1" component, the component prompts your browser to download an image of this component from Google. Through this process, Google is informed precisely which page of our website is being visited. As specified by Google, your visit undergoes additional analysis in the event you are not logged into your Google account. If you access our site while logged into Google and press the "+1" button, Google can collect information about your Google account, websites you recommend as well as your IP address, along with other browser-related information. This allows your "+1" recommendation to be stored and publicized. Your Google "+1" recommendation can then appear as a reference in other Google services, such as search results, your Google account or other places, such as on websites and ads in the internet, together with your account name and, if applicable, a picture you provided to Google. Furthermore, Google can link your visit to our site with data stored by Google. Google also records this information for the purpose of further improving Google services. If you wish to minimize the collection of information by Google as previously described, you must log out of your Google account before visiting our website.  
You can access Google‘s data protection policies relating to the "+1" button together with all relevant information on the collection, transfer and use of data by Google, your rights in this regard as well as your profile settings options at the following link: <https://developers.google.com/+/web/buttons-policy>

### Use of Facebook components

Our website employs components provided by facebook.com. Facebook is a service of Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. 

Each time our website receives an access request equipped with a Facebook component, the component prompts your browser to download an image of this Facebook component. Through this process, Facebook is informed precisely which page of our website is being visited. 

When you access our site while logged into Facebook, Facebook uses information gathered by this component to identify the precise page you are viewing and associates this information to your personal account on Facebook. Whenever you click on the "Like" button, for example, or enter a comment, this information is transmitted to your personal account on Facebook and stored there. In addition, Facebook is informed of your visit to our website. This occurs regardless of whether you click on a component or not. 

If you wish to prevent the transfer to and storage of data by Facebook about you and your interaction with our website, you must first log out of Facebook before visiting our website. The data protection policies of Facebook provide additional information, in particular about the collection and use of data by Facebook, your rights in this regard as well as the options available to you for protecting your privacy: <https://de-de.facebook.com/about/privacy/>

In addition, tools are freely available on the market that can be used to block Facebook social plug-ins with add-ons from being added to all commonly used browsers: <http://webgraph.com/resources/facebookblocker/> You can find an overview of Facebook plugins at <https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>

### Use of Twitter recommendation components

Our website employs components provided by Twitter. Twitter is a service of Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. Each time our website receives an access request equipped with a Twitter component, the component prompts your browser to download an image of this component from Twitter. Through this process, Twitter is informed precisely which page of our website is being visited. We have no control over the data that Twitter collects in the process, or over the extent of the data that Twitter collects. To the best of our knowledge, Twitter collects the URL of each website accessed as well as the IP address of the user, but does so solely for the purpose of displaying Twitter components. Additional information may be obtained from the Twitter data privacy policy, at: <http://twitter.com/privacy>. 

You may change your data privacy settings in your account settings, at <http://twitter.com/account/settings>.

### Use of Google-Adwords

For purposes of promotion, our website also employs the Google ad tool "Google-Adwords". As part of this, our website employs the analysis service "Conversion-Tracking" from Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, hereinafter referred to as "Google". If you access our site by way of a Google ad, a cookie is placed on your computer. Cookies are small text files that your internet browser downloads and stores to your computer. These so-called "conversion cookies" cease to be active after 30 days and are not used to identify you personally. If you visit certain pages of our website while the cookie is still active, we and Google know that you, as user, have clicked on ads placed on Google and were redirected to our site. Google uses the information obtained through "conversion cookies" to compile statistics for our website. These statistics tell us the total number of users who have clicked on our ad as well as which pages of our site were then accessed by each user. However, neither we nor other advertisers who use "Google-Adwords" receive any kind of information that can be used to personally identify users. You can prevent the installation of "conversion cookies" by making the appropriate change to your browser settings, for example by setting your browser so that the automatic placement of cookies is deactivated or by blocking cookies from the domain "googleadservices.com". You can obtain the relevant data privacy policy from Google at the following link: <https://services.google.com/sitestats/de.html>

### Use of Google AdSense

Our website employs Google AdSense. Google AdSense is a service of Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, for incorporating advertisements. Google-AdSense uses so-called "cookies", text files, that are stored to your computer and which provide analysis of the use of our website. Furthermore, Google AdSense uses so-called "web beacons". Web beacons allow Google to analyze information, such as visitor traffic to our website. This information, along with your IP address and the ad format displayed, is transmitted to Google in the US where it is stored and may be transferred by Google to contracting partners. However, Google does not merge your IP-address with other stored data on you. You can prevent cookies from being installed by adjusting the settings on your browser software accordingly. You should be aware, however, that by doing so you may not be able to make full use of all the functions of our website. By using our website you declare that you agree to the processing of data collected about you by Google in the manner previously described and for the purposes there specified.
